BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.840044: Toledo Board of Education (classified employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2, Local 272, Local 349, Local 840, 2000-2003 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Code no.840045: Middlesex County NJ (roads & parks) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 3440, 1993-2001 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Code no.840046: New Jersey University of Medicine & Dentistry (faculty) and American Association of University Professors, 1995- 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Code no.840047: Washoe County NV School District (classified) and Nevada Classified School Employees Association, Ch. 2, 2000- 2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Code no.840048: Port Authority of NY & NJ (agents & toll collectors) and Transport Workers Union of America, Local 1400, 1993-1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Code no.840049: Community Consolidated School District 54 (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Code no.840050: Springfield School District #186 (teachers) and Springfield Education Association, 1994-2002 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Code no.840051: Cherry Hill (teachers & others) and Cherry Hill Education Association, 1996-2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Code no.840052: Ann Arbor School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1994-2003 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Code no.840054: New York City Transit Authority (supervisors) and Subway Surface Supervisors Association, 1991-1998 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Code no.840056: San Francisco Municipal Railway (transit operations) and Transport Workers Union of America, Local 250-A, 1991- 2004 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Code no.840057: Chicago, City of (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters / Chicago Fire Fighters Union, Local 2, 1992- 1999 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Code no.840058: Woodbridge NJ Board of Education (teachers & support) and Woodbridge Township Education Association, 1993-2003 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Code no.840060: Chicago, City of (public safety alliance) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1991-1999 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Code no.840061: Chicago, City of (labor & crAmerican Federation of Teacherss-Alliance) and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 76, Local 1001, Local 1092, 1992-1999 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Code no.840062: New York City Housing Authority (white collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1991-2003 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Code no.840063: Volusia County Board of Education (noninstruct) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 850, 2001-2003 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Code no.840064: Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority and Transport Workers Union of America, Local 234, 1988- 2004 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Code no.840069: Metropolitan Council/Metro Transit (Operations) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1005, 1995-1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Code no.840072: Washington DC Metro Transit Authority (operations, maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 689, 1998- 2001 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Code no.840076: Tri- Met Transit Authority (drivers & mechanics) and Amalgamated Transit Union, District 757, 1994- 1998 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Code no.840085: Missouri-IL Metro District Transit (operators & maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 788, 1987- 1998 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Code no.840086: Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 732, 1984-1997 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Code no.840087: District of Columbia (master) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 20, 1989- 1990 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Code no.840088: Bay Area Rapid Transit (maintenance, clerical, & professional) and Service Employees International Union, Local 790, 1994-2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Code no.840089: Bay Area Rapid Transit (bus drivers & operators) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1555, 1988- 2001 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Code no.840090: Massachusetts, University of (administrative clerical, & technical) and National Education Association / University Staff Association - Massachussets Teachers Association, 1995-2001 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Code no.840103: New York City Transit Authority (buses-Queens) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1056, 1994-2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Code no.840104: Metropolitan (Houston) Transit Authority and Transport Workers Union of America, Local 260, 1994-2002 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Code no.840107: New York City Housing Authority and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 237, 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Code no.840108: New York City Housing Authority (patrol officers) and Housing Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1982-1987 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Code no.840109: New York State Thruway Authority (unit #1) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 72, 1992-1999 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Code no.840110: Dade County, Metropolitan (Aviation Dept.) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1542, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Code no.840111: Maine, University of (clerical, office, lab & technical) and National Education Association, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Code no.840112: Connecticut State (social & human services-unit P2) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 4 Locals, 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Code no.840113: Los Angeles Unified School District (skilled crafts- Unit E) and Los Angeles County Building and Construction Trades Council, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Code no.321: Seagrams, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, 1996-2003 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Code no.419: Wise Foods and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 1776, 1989-2005 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Code no.645: Westpoint Stevens and UNITE HERE, Local 1948, 1994-2003 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Code no.859: Cloak & Suit Trucking Assn, et al. (5 Assns) and UNITE HERE, Local 98, Local 102, Local 132, 2001-2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Code no.1225: MeadWestvaco Corp., Rumford Mill/Mead Papers and Professional Association for Contract Employees, Local 900, 1989- 1995 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Code no.1230: U.S. Alliance, Coosa Pines Corp. (Kimberly-Clark) and Professional Association for Contract Employees, Local 69, Local 216, Local 595, Local 931, 1994-2004 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Code no.1900: U.S. Alliance, Coosa Pines Corp. (Kimberly-Clark) and United Paperworkers International Union /Professional Association for Contract Employees, Local 692, Local 1595, Local 1693, 1998-2004 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Code no.1901: Toshiba Display Devices Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1632, 1995-2004 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Code no.2315: Kimble Glass and United Steel Workers of America, 1995-2004 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Code no.2521: National Steel Corp and United Steel Workers of America, 1996-2004 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Code no.2522: National Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, Local 16, Local 30, Local 67, Local 68, 1996-2004 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Code no.2523: National Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1996-2004 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Code no.2539: LTV Steel Co & LTV Steel Tabular Products Co and United Steel Workers of America, 1994-1999 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Code no.2561: LTV Steel Co & LTV Steel Tabular Products Co and United Steel Workers of America, 1995-2004 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Code no.3609: Allen Bradley Co and United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America, 1987-2002 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Code no.3625: Westinghouse and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Code no.3660: Thomson Multimedia Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1160, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Code no.3695: Raytheon Co. (production & maintenance) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1505, 1989- 1991 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Code no.4065: McDonell Douglas and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 720, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Code no.4066: McDonell Douglas and United Auto Workers, Local 148, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Code no.4067: Boeing Co. (was McDonnell Douglas) and International Association of Machinists / Southern California Professional Engineering Association, Lodge 725, 1987-2002 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Code no.4115: Volvo Trucks North America Inc, New River Valley Plant and United Auto Workers, Local 2069, 1999-2005 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Code no.4197: New United Motor Manufacturing, Inc. and United Auto Workers, Local 2244, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Code no.4427: Xerox Corp. and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, Local 14A, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Code no.5212: National Master Freight Agreement and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Code no.5255: United Parcel Service and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Code no.5402: Ocean Going Cargo Vessel and National Maritime Union, 1969-1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Code no.5407: Tanker Companies and National Maritime Union, 1969-1984 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Code no.5772: AT & T (Partial CBA) and Communication Workers of America, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Code no.6342: Stop & Shop Supermarket Company and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 919, 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Code no.6352: Greater St. Louis Food Employers' Council and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 655, 2003-2007 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Code no.6356: Adam's Super Food Stores, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 371, 1996-2004 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Code no.6736: Greater St. Louis Food Employers' Council and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 655, 1994-2007 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Code no.7418: The Depository Trust Company and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153, 1990- 2004 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Code no.8220: Blue Cross-Blue Shield of IL and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 743, 1995-2001 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Code no.8221: Saturn and United Auto Workers, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Code no.8222: Mazda and United Auto Workers, Local 3000, 1988-1994 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Code no.8223: Bituminous Coal and United Mine Workers of America, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Code no.8224: National Master Automobile Transporters and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1985-1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Code no.8225: General Motors and United Auto Workers, 1990-1993 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Code no.8226: United Parcel Service (Controlled Substances Testing) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Code no.8227: Borg-Wanner Corp. (Leave - Arrest) and United Auto Workers, 1990-1995 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Code no.8228: Arcata Graphics (Leave - Civil Air Patrol) and Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers, 1991-1996 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Code no.8229: Ford Electronics & Refrigeration Corp. (Leave - Civil Defense) and International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers, 1991-1995 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Code no.8230: General Motors Corp. (Leave - Community Service) and United Auto Workers, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Code no.8231: Dunlop Tire & Rubber Corp. (Leave - Community Service) and United Rubber Workers, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Code no.8232: Michigan Corrections Organization and Service Employees International Union, Local 526-M, 1992-2001 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Code no.800001: MIamii-Dade County Public Schools (adminstrators) and American Federation of School Administrators, Local 77, 1998- 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Code no.800013: State of New Jersey (state colleges) and American Federation of Teachers, 1995-1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Code no.800144: Massachussets Higher Education Coordinating Council (community colleges) and National Education Association, 1996- 1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Code no.800229: State of Alaska (general government employees) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 52, 2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Code no.800294: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (corrections) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 13, 1998-2001 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Code no.800313: State of Florida (nurses) and Florida Nurses Association, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Code no.800335: State of Florida (human services, professional, operational, administrative, and clerical units) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 79, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Code no.800359: State of Michigan (professional employees) and Michigan Professional Employees Society, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Code no.800366: State of Michigan (principal agencies) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 25, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Code no.800378: University of Minnesota and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 320, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Code no.800382: State of Connecticut (administrative clerical unit) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 196, Local 318, Local 355, Local 478, 1994-1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Code no.800409: State of Michigan (technical unit) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Code no.800423: City of San Antonio, Texas (police officers) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1994-1998 (Box 41, Folder 13)